Finding Aid for Vice President and Chief Financial Officer (University of Michigan) Records, 1909-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Associate Vice President for Finance
  - Topical Files, 1996-2006
    - 1996-2006, 1998-2003
      - Students Organizing for Labor Economic Equality (SOLE), 2002-2003 (Box 159)
      - Survey Responses, UM, 2002 (Box 159)
      - Taubman College of Architecture and Urban Planning, 2003 (Box 159)
      - Technology Management Office (TMO), 2000-2002 (Box 159)
      - Temporary Staffing Services (TSS) -- Cost Study, 1999-2002 (Box 159)
      - Trademark, 2002 (Box 159)
      - Trust Agreement, University, 2002 (Box 159)
      - Union Contracts, 2002-2003 (Box 159)
      - United States Department of Education, 2002 (Box 159)
      - University Investment Pool / Equity (UIP), 2000-2003
        - General (Box 159)
        - Administrative Expenses (Box 159)
        - Dental School Distribution Changes (Box 159)
        - Distribution Rate (Box 159)
        - Equipment Leasing (Box 159)
        - UIP Invested in LTP (Box 159)
      - University Press, 2003 (Box 159)
      - Vacation Accrual, 2001-2003 (Box 159)
      - Walgreen Drama Center, 2002-2003 (Box 159)
  - Topical Files, 1992-2005; 1999-2004
    The 2008 accession includes primarily materials from Timothy Slottow's tenure in the position. As with previous accessions, there is some overlap with the Central Topical Files, as well as some materials unique to the AVPF office. Significant subject include metrics, purchasing, and the AVPF office.
    - 1979-2005, 1998-2003
      - AVPF Senior Staff Retreat, 2003
      - Financial Op. and Cont. -- Delegation of Authority, 2001-2003
      - Financial Op. and Cont. -- Misc., 2003
      - Accounts Payable and Travel Office, 2002-2003 (Box 223)
      - Accounts Receivable -- Miscellaneous, 2004-2005 (Box 223)
      - Accounts Receivable -- Business Case, 2001-2003 (Box 223)
      - AIMS Meetings, 2004-2005 (Box 223)
      - Alumni Association, 2002-2003 (Box 223)
      - Athletics -- Budget, Miscellaneous, 2003-2005 (Box 223)
      - Audits -- University, 2004-2005; 2 folders (Box 223)
      - AVPF ELT Meetings, 2004 (Box 223)
      - AVPF ELT Meetings, 2005 (Box 223)
      - AVPF HR, 2003-2004 (Box 223)
      - AVPF Performance Summary, 2003-2004 (Box 224)
      - AVPF -- Purchasing (Miscellaneous), 2002-2003 (Box 224)
      - AVPF Senior Staff Retreat, 2004-2005 (Box 224)
      - Cashier's Office, 2001-2002 (Box 224)
      - CFO Senior Staff Meeting, 2005 (Box 224)
      - Closings, 2004 (Box 224)
      - Closings, 2005 (Box 224)
      - COI, 2004 (Box 224)
      - COI, 2005 (Box 224)
      - Critical Initiatives, 2001-2003 (Box 224)
      - Debt Capacity, 2004-2005 (Box 224)
      - E-Procurement, 1999-2002 (Box 224)
      - Ethics, 2004-2005 (Box 225)
      - Finance & Capital Projects, 2004; 3 folders 1 .ppt file (Box 225)
      - Finance & Capital Projects, 2005; 2 folders (Box 225)
      - Finance Audit Committee, 2004 (Box 225)
      - Financial Controls Framework Taskforce, 1998-2004 (Box 225)
      - Financial Operations, 1999-2004 (Box 225)
      - Financial Forum, 2005 (Box 226)
      - General Council, Office of, 2003-2004 (Box 226)
      - HHC, 2000-2005 (Box 226)
      - HR -- Miscellaneous, 2004-2005; 2 folders (Box 226)
      - HRMS, 2005-, 2 folders (Box 226)
      - Human Capital Report, 2005 (Box 226)
      - ICAG, 2005 (Box 226)
      - Internal Bank Meeting, 2002-2005; 2 folders (Box 226)
      - Internal Bank Meeting, 2002-2005; 2 folders (Box 227)
      - Internal Controls, 2005 (Box 227)
      - IT Security, 2004-2005 (Box 227)
      - LSI, 2003-2005; 2 folders (Box 227)
      - Mail Service, 1996-2002 (Box 227)
      - MAIS, 2004-2005; 2 folders (Box 227)
      - Metrics (Box 228)
        - Presentation, 2005 (Box 228)
        - Financial Operations, 1999-2002 (Box 228)
        - Procurement, 1999-2002 (Box 228)
        - Payroll, 1999-2002 (Box 228)
        - Purchasing, 2001-2003 (Box 228)
        - Sponsored Programs, 2001-2003 (Box 228)
        - Treasurer's Office, 2001-2002 (Box 228)
      - MCARE, 2003-2006; 2 folders (Box 228)
      - MStores, 2000-2003 (Box 228)
      - Optical Imaging, 2002-2003 (Box 228)
      - Payroll Office, 2001-2003 (Box 228)
      - Financial/Physical Resource CPU, 1999-2002 (Box 229)
      - Photographs (Photographs of official ceremonies and events. People include, Anna Curtenius Roosevelt, John Engler, Sandra Day O'Conner, Robert Altman, Bill Gray, Jessye Norman, Homer Neal), circa 1996 (Box 229)
      - Procurement,1999-2004 (Box 229)
      - Procurement -- Re-engineering, 1999-2002 (Box 229)
      - Purchasing, Stores and Auxiliary Services, 1995-2004; 2 folders (Box 229)
      - Purchasing, Stores and Auxiliary Services -- Vendor Ethics, 2000-2004 (Box 229)
      - Purchasing, Stores and Auxiliary Services -- Travel Management (Box 229)
      - Purchasing, Stores and Auxiliary Services -- Prime Vendor Contracts, 2001 (Box 229)
      - Space Analysis, 1992-2003 (Box 229)
      - Student Financial Operations (Student Accounts, Miscellaneous), 2000-2003 (Box 229)
      - Tax Department, 2002-2003 (Box 229)
      - Treasurer's Office, 2002-2005 (Box 230)
      - Utilities, 2003-2005 (Box 230)
      - Vendor Diversity, 2001-2002 (Box 230)
      - Work Connections, 2001-2002 (Box 230)
      - Student Affairs, Office of (Miscellaneous), 2002-2003 (Box 230)
      - Surveys -- Miscellaneous, 2002- (Box 230)
      - Women (Report on the Status of Women, Faculty Women's Club), 1999-2004 (Box 230)
- Photographs
  - Photographs of Financial Officers (Box 143)
    - Shirley W. Smith (Box 143)
    - Robert P. Briggs (Box 143)
    - Wilber K. Pierpont (Box 143)
    - James F. Brinkerhoff (Box 143)
    - Farris W. Womack (Box 143)